
Function: getAccName(domElement)

Description: Returns the accessible name computation for both the Name and Description properties in accordance with the latest W3C AccName Prototype algorithm.
https://github.com/WhatSock/w3c-alternative-text-computation

Returns: Object with properties: "name", "desc", and "error"

Note: This is not the same as the getText() method, but rather explicitly follows the algorithm set forth in the AccName computation for computing Names and Descriptions within browsers. In accordance with the W3C AccName specification, an element may only have an accessible name if it meets the definition of specific criteria. The getAccName function does not support chaining.
For further details regarding the AccName algorithm, visit: https://github.com/whatsock/w3c-alternative-text-computation

Example:

// Compute the name of a form field
var accessibleName = $A.getAccName(domElement).name;

// Compute the description of a form field
var accessibleDescription = $A.getAccName(domElement).desc;
